Ernestine Gilbreth Carey Papers, 1915-2005
Sophia Smith Collection
- General (Box 15)
  - Philippines, 1956-78 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Scotland-Stowe College, 1980-85 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Union/Russia, 1980-93 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Sweden, 1967-87 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Alphabetical (Box 24)
    - A, 1962-95 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Abdelsamad, Moustafa, 1997, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Abrams, Bonnie, 1980-81 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Alchon, Guy, University of Delaware, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Altrusa Club of New York, 1952-90 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Amelung, Marion Kent (Mrs. Charles), 1978-94 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - American Institute of Industrial Engineers, 1974-75 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - American Management Association (Box 25)
      - General, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Appley, Lawrence, 1978-91 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Ferrin, Allan, 1978-1982 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Hayes, James L., 1978-96 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - American Psychological Association, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers (Box 25)
      - Belanger, Don, 1981-82 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Beldon, David, 1984-95 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Davies, Clarence, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Finch, Roger, 1978-82 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Garvin-Donahue, Carron, 1975-88 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Habach, George, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Jacklitsch, Jack, 1978-81 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Perrin, Arthur, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Rosinski, Walt, 1978-81 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Sillcox, Lewis K., 1954-83 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Thomas, Frederick, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - General Correspondence, 1935-84 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Miscellaneous, 1934-84 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Arizona State University, 1981-83 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Army, U.S. Dept. of, 1978-83 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Association of Marquette University Women, 1966-71 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Auburn University, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Authors Guild/Authors League Fund, 1974-91 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Authors Guild Correspondence, 1955-72 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - B, 1955-98 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Bach, Muriel, 1978-89 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Barany, James, 1994-95 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Barnes, Ralph- UCLA, 1969-95 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Barnum, Jerome, 1969-81 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Battles, Richard, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Bedian, Arthur, Louisiana State University, 1990-95 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Bell and Howell, Micro Photo Division, 1967-82 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Beldon, David, 1997-99 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Berdahl, Ella May, U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Bettman, Otto, Bettman Archives, 1978-81 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Black, J.T., Auburn University, 1981-95 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Bolton, Al A., 1989-91 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Brandeau, Margaret, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Braum, Daniel, 1978-85 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Brown University, undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Burnham, Donald C., Westinghouse, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Burnes, John-Editor, Industrial Management, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Bursley/Towne family, 1968-87 [See also: University of Michigan] (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Butts, Bill, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Byrnes, Mary (Mrs. Maurice), 1979-91 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Bedeian, Arthur G., 1990-92 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - C, 1948-2003 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Cantor, Ruth, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Callahan, Jane, 1966-1987 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - California State University-Fresno, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Carney, Ann (Mrs. John J.), 1979 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Carlberg, Bo and Dorothy, 1962-89 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Carroll, Mrs. Philip, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Carroll Center for the Blind, 1970-82 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Chervenik, Emily M., 1978-95 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Chisolm, Phyllis, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Council for International Progress in Management, 1970-72 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Columbia University,1985 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Congdon, Don, 1924-86 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Cook, Alice, 1970-72 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Cornell University, 1978-94 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - D, 1950-2002 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Daniels, Marge (Mrs. Ed), 1970-82 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Dartmouth College, Dick Hall's House (Box 27)
      - General, 1971-1990 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Fiftieth anniversary poem by Lillian Moller Gilbreth, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Davis, Philip, 1983-83 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Deming, W. Edwards, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - De Paul University, Prof. John E. Burns, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Diebold, Inc., 1982-90 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Drucker, Peter, 1957-80 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Durant, Eugenie, 1984-87 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Dvorak, Hermione, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - E, 1954-88 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Eastwood, Anne, 1991-93 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Eastman Kodak Company, 1979-82 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Eisendrath, David, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Emerson, Howard P., University of Tennessee, 1978-80 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Emory University, 1980-84 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Engelburger, Joseph, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Engineering and Science Hall of Fame, 1986-88 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Exton, William, March 1968-Feb.1984 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - F, 1956-91 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Fein, Mitchell, 1983-84 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Fenster, Saul, New Jersey Institute of Technology, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Feorene, Orlando J., 1984-92 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Foegen, J.H., Winona State University, 1978-96 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - G, 1956-2001 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - General Electric Company (Box 28)
      - General, 1925-96, undated (Box 28, Folder 20-21)
      - Smiddy, Harold F., 1956-82 (Box 28, Folder 23)
      - Miscellaneous 1928-84 (Box 28, Folder 24)
      - Kitchens for the Handicapped, 1979, undated (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Gage, James A, 1981-83 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Georgia Institute of Technology, 1981-94 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Girard, Mary and Richard, 1981-83 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Girl Scouts of America, 1971-87 (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
    - Giroux, Robert, Farrar, Strauss and Giroux Inc., 1980-81 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Gladstone, Kate, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Goetz, Billy, 1978-78 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Golden Gate University, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Goldstein, Irving R., 1970-83 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Gomberg, William, 1979-81 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Goodgold, Joseph, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Gottlieb, M.S., UCLA Department of Engineering, 1950-80 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Graham, Ben and Gladys, 1970-89 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Greenwood, Ronald, 1973-95, undated (Box 29, Folder 14-16)
    - Green, James, 1980-83 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Griffin, Annie Eisenmann, 1965-79 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Griffith, Colonel Ole, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Groseclose, Frank, 1949-83 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Grossman, Michael, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - H, 1957-2000 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Hansen, Arthur, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Hansl, Eva, 1966-84 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Hardkopf, Jewel, Librarian Management Consultant, 1955-80 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Harvard-Radcliffe, Schlesinger Library, 1982-83 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Haynes, Wesley, 1978-93 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Hazelton, Helen, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Heady, Ferrel, 1953-79 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Higgins, William and Florence, 1992-95 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Hilton, Eunice, Syracuse University, 1950-79 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Holcomb, Jarold Romeyn, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Hoover, Hubert, 1950-96 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Hopf, Harry, undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Hunt, Kathryn, 1994-95 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - IBM, 1940-82 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Institute of Management Services, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - J, 1953-86 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Jaffe, William, 1971-95, undated (Box 31-32, Folder 2-26)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Johns Hopkins University Press, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Johnson, Lewis Jerome, Harvard, 1993, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Johnson and Johnson, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Jude, George, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Juran, Joseph, 1982-94 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - K, 1955-2003 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Karger, Delmar W., 1980-82 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Kent, Grace, 1971-94 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Kersting, Fred, 1964-84 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Koenig, Carolyn Dewett, 1982-84 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Koontz, Dr., 1979 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Kruger, Bernie, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - L, 1956-99 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Ladd, Helen Douglas, 1961-93 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Ladd, Paul Jr., 1994 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Landis, James N., 1978-91 (Box 33, Folder 17-18)
    - Laster, Owen, 1982-95 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Lederer, Albrecht M., 1978 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Lehrer, Robert, 1982-87 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Lemke, Antje Bultman, 1993-94 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Liebold, Peter, 1979-95 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Libraries, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Lies, Eugenia B., 1945-91 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Lindstrom, Richard, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Linn's Stamp News, 1982-84 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Lohieke, Franz, Louisiana State University, 1978-91 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Louden, Keith, 1940-94 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Lovell, Gordon, 1978-81 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Loyola Marymount University, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - M, 1949-94, undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - MacFarland, Ellen, 1983-84 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Maine, University of, 1946-90 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Maital, Shlomo, 1984-93 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Major, Nathaniel, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Malcolm, Donald G., 1986-89 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Mandel, Mike, 1971-93 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Manhasset Public Library, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Margaret Sanger Papers Project, 1951-94 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Marquette University, 1990, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - May, Elizabeth, 1953-84 (Box 35, Folder 4-6)
    - Mayer, Ysrael (Irwin), Hive Publishing Company, 1979-95 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Maynard, Harold M. (Box 35)
      - Correspondence, 1959-69 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Motion-Time Management (MTM), 1940-91 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Mayo Clinic, 1961-83 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - McCormick, Emily, 1993-94 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - McCormick, Ernest, 1978-90, undated (Box 35, Folder 12-13)
    - McFaddon, Mattie F., 1984-94 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Co., 1963-81 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - McIntyre, Douglas, 1982-87 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - McLean, Anne, Library of Congress, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Menninger Clinic, 1962-78, undated (Box 36, Folder 5-6)
    - Merrick, Charles, Lafayette College, 1969-80 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Merrill, Dot, 1952-87 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Meyer, Helen, 1985-90 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Michigan, University of, 1980-85 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Michigan Technological University, 2000-02 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Mills College, 1952-82 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Minnesota, University of, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, unidentified, undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Mitchell, Norma, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1918-81, undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Mize, Joseph 1978-90 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Mobley, Emily, Purdue University Libraries 1984-93 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Morgensen, Allan H., 1980-88 (Box 37, Folder 3-4)
    - Molloy, Julie (Mrs. Ernest), 1979 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Montag, Geraldine, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Montclair Public Library, 1954-84 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Montclair State College, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Moore, James M., 1979-80 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Moore, Leo B., 1978-81 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Morley, Jane, 1991-93 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Mount Holyoke Alumnae Association, 1985-92 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Mount Mary College, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Mundel, Marvin, 1978-91 (Box 37, Folder 14-15)
    - Mullee, William, 1968-85 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1978-81 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Myers, Clark E., 1959-83 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - N, 1959-2000 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Nadler, Gerald, 1966-2002 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Nadworny, Milton J., 1955, 1983-92 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
    - Nagel, Carl E., 1981-82 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - National Academy of Engineering, 2001-02 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - National Women's Hall of Fame, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Naylor, James C., 1992 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Neal, Jean, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Neely family, 1963-83 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Newman, Louis and Ruth S., 1978-79 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - New England Butt Company, 1978-91 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - New Jersey Institute of Technology, 1975-84 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - New School for Social Research, 1978-82 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - New York Times Book Review, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - New Yorker, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Niebel, Benjamin, 1979-92 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Niles, Mary Cushing, 1954-86 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Nissley, Harold, 1940-93 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Nordlund, Donald, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Northern Telecom, Inc., 1982 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Northeastern University, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Northwestern University, 1984-85 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - O, 1962-99 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Oakland, California, City of, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Oakland Tribune, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - O'Connor, Mary Martin, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Ott, Dudley, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - P, 1965-2000 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Parker, Ellen, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Patton, John A., 1971-87 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - P.E.N. (Poets, Essayists, and Novelists), 1965-2002 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania State University, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Perloff, Robert, 1994-96 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Perkins, James, 1979-95 (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
    - Petersen, Peter, 1985-91 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Philanthropy/activism, 1985-97 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Phoenix Public Library, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Pinsky, Robert, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Pollock, Ruth Leach, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Porter, David, 1968-71 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Potter, Andrey A., 1945-75 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Potter, Helen, 1968-90 (Box 39, Folder 14-16)
    - Political correspondence, 1969-2003 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Pryer, Roberta, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Purdue University (Box 40)
      - Publications, 1985-2000 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence (Box 40)
        - Industrial Engineering, 1989-2002 (Box 40, Folder 4)
        - Amarine, Harold, 1969-1992 (Box 40, Folder 5)
        - Compton, Dale, 1988-2002 (Box 40, Folder 6)
        - Dagnese, Joseph, 1972-1988 (Box 40, Folder 7)
        - Daniels, Jane, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 8)
        - Dowden, Keith, 1979-89 (Box 40, Folder 9)
        - Greene, James, 1969-1980 (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - Hansen, Arthur D., 1976-1981 (Box 41, Folder 2)
        - Leimkuhler, Ferdinand, 1983-88 (Box 41, Folder 3)
        - Markee, Katherine, 1998-2001 (Box 41, Folder 4)
        - Moses, David, 1968-84 (Box 41, Folder 5)
        - Nof, Shimon, 1979-84 (Box 41, Folder 6)
        - Shepard, George, 1981-83 (Box 41, Folder 7)
        - Schroyer, Helen, 1974-92 (Box 41, Folder 8)
        - Thomas, Marlin, 1997-2001 (Box 41, Folder 9)
        - Library, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 10)
        - Press, 1977-93 (Box 41, Folder 11)
        - Miscellaneous, 1972-95 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Quick, J. H., 1979 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - R, 1940-67 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Rathe, Alex, 1978-98 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Reid, Helen Ogden, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1962-78 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Reynolds, Nancy Z., 1972-83 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Rhode Island, University of, 1962-95 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Ricciardi, Michael, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Richardson, Wallace J., 1979-88 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Riley, Russell L., 1982-1984 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Robinson, Alan, 1990-93 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Rockwell International, 1978-82 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Roe, Joseph, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Rosenberger, Donald M., 1983 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Roy, Robert, 1978-1992 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Rusk, Howard, 1972-78 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - S, 1951-92 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Sachem Publishing Associates, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Schleman, Helen, 1970-88 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Schroyer, Helen, 1977-95 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Schultz, Duane, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Schwab, John L., 1965-86 (Box 42, Folder 22-23)
    - Scripps College, 1946-90 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Seaton, Margaret, 1964-81 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Segur, A. B., 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Seventh Day Adventist Church, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Slifer, Rose Jeanne, 1967-91 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Shaw, Anne, 1949-65 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Smalley, Harold E., 1972-91 (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
    - Smith, Michael, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Smithsonian Institution, National Portrait Gallery, 1972-2002 (Box 43, Folder 8-11)
    - Snyder, Marvin B., 1996 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Society for the Advancement of Management, 1996-2001 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Society of Women Engineers, 2000-2003 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Spofford, Dorothy, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Spriegel, William, 1969-84 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Srbich, Alexander, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Stanford University, 1969-91 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Steinmetz Award, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Stelling, John D., 1990-91 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Stepanich, Mary Ellen, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Stokes, Mary, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Stoops, Thomas, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Stratton, Dorothy, 1972-94 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Straus, Mr. Jack I., 1979 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Sullivan, Lucille, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Syracuse University, 1981-82 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Szostak, Rick, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - T, 1957-78 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Tabor, Peggy, 1958-79 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Tappan, Frances, 1978-80 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Tichauer, E. R., 1969-84 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Tietjen, Jill S., 1996-2001 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Tiffin, Joseph, 1979-83 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Time Lapse Photography, Inc., 1979-81 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Thompson, Thompson and Lichtner, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Trescott. Martha, 1983-93 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Trotti, Louise, 1950-80 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Tuttle, Eleanor, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - U, 1954-67 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - University of Arizona, 1968-75 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1977-93 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - University of Delaware, 1987-89 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - University of Indiana, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - University of Massachusetts, Amherst, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - University of Michigan, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - University of New South Wales, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - University of Notre Dame, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1955-85 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - V, 1969-2003 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Vance, Stanley, 1982-83 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Viscardi, Henry, 1966-78 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Vormelker, Rose L., 1971-79 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Vough, Mr. Clair F., 1983-85 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - W, 1963-93 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Waggoner, Neva, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Wall, Jessie, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Wallace, Lawrence W., 1949-79 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Wall Street Journal, Letters to Editor, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Warburg, Wilma (Mrs. Frederick M.), 1973-79 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Warren, Gertrude and Glenn, 1970-79 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Washington University at St. Louis, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Webb, Ella, 1970-80 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Webster, June Bricker, 1965, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Welch, Maureen, 1959-85 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1982-84 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Weston, Nancy, 1974-84 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - West Virginia University, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Wilkinson, George D., 1979-85 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Wrege, Charles, 1979-83 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Wren, Daniel, 1981-93 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - X-Z, 1967-2001 (Box 45, Folder 33)
- SERIES III. WRITINGS
  - Books (Box 45)
    - "As Silver is Tried" (unpublished, c.1960s) (Box 45)
      - Key to EGC color coded research folders (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Infant and child growth and development (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Obstetrics (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Medical (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Medicine (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Nursing history (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Pediatrics (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Nurses' training (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Nurses: general notes (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Homes for unwed mothers (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Maternal health (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Heart patients (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Personnel administration (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Catholicism (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - Franco-American data (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Communism (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Protestant thought (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Seasons and nature (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Summary of dates and weather conditions (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Massachusetts history (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - New England expressions (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Superstitions and proverbs (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Dogs (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Movies and fashions of 1920s (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Boston (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Railroading and Ben Crew (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Quotes used (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Whole book planning (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - New notes last chapters (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - Character development, outline and notes (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - Ages and character notes (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - Grammy Allen (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - General info (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - Gist of book (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - "After Death" (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Chapter notes (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Part 3 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Plot development (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Diary on as "Silver is Tried," 1962-65, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence., 1961-67 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Photos and images (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Belles on Their Toes 1950 (Box 48)
      - Belles chapter summaries (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Promotional literature, 1972-89, undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Copyright renewal, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Final draft, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Fan mail, 1952-2001 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Cheaper by the Dozen 1948 (Box 48)
      - Book (Box 48)
        - Publicity, 1949-2000 (Box 49, Folder 1)
        - Japanese edition, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 2)
        - Contract, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Movie (Box 49)
        - Publicity, 1964-2003 (Box 49, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence, 1949-52 (Box 49, Folder 5)
        - Remake, 1996-2006 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Stage play (Box 49)
        - Script, 1961 (2 copies) (Box 49, Folder 7)
        - Musical scores, 1970-82 (Box 49, Folder 8)
        - Publicity and play bills, 1971-2002 (Box 49, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence, 1961-90 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous, 1979-2002 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Fan mail, 1948-2005 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Fan mail, 1948-2005 (Box 50-50c)
        [See also OVERSIZE MATERIALS.]
    - Giddy Moment 1958 (Box 50)
      - Books sent to family and friends, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 1)